<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Android Application FPS Recording</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/android_fps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/android_fps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-to-record-an-applications-fps-frames-per-second-data-on-android-devices-without-root-access&#34;&gt;How to record an application&amp;rsquo;s FPS (Frames per Second) data on Android devices without root access&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When conducting experiment on our training script&amp;rsquo;s effect on mobile application&amp;rsquo;s performance, we hit a barrier because conventional method to dump frame rate requires root access to the phone; however, it is very hard if not impossible to get root on US versions of Samsung S25 Ultra because Samsung locked OEM settings. As a result, we need to acquire information needed using dumpsys. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with an example using Genshin Impact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freelist Memory Buffer Allocator</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/freelist_memory_scheduling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/freelist_memory_scheduling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In modern computer systems, memory is one of the most precious and constrained resources — a limitation that&amp;rsquo;s especially pronounced in the era of artificial intelligence. In the domain of on-device training, memory bottleneck have become one of the hardest obstacle to overcome; neural networks are notoriously memory hungry, especially during backpropagation, which involves storing and manipulating large amounts of intermediate data. Devices with 8GB RAM often struggle to survive, and the situation is even more dire for smaller, resource-constrained hardware.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Love Bananas</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/banana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/banana/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bananas are great because&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
